Finding Aid for Ernest Hemingway Collection
Clarke Historical Library
- Ernest Hemingway Collection
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Paterson, Kenneth H. Hemingway’s Cuba,1999 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Plummer, William. Papa comes in from the critical cold at Hemingway revival in balmy Key West,1985 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Prescott, Helen. Hemingway’s Michigan,1985 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Roberts, MacLean. (An) afternoon with Papa Hemingway,1957 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Ross, Lillian. Hemingway told me things, notes on ten years of correspondence,1999 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Rybovich, John. Clash of the Titans,circa 1982 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Scalzo, Jim. Hemingway’s Cuba,1997 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Simon, Jane. Wisps of Hemingway,2002 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Steele, Lori Hall. Hemingway’s Windemere,1997 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Stevens, Stuart. (A) fine line: Hemingway’s works reveal the likeness of skiing then and now,1986 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Swift, E.M. In the country he loved,198? (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Swoyer, Megan. On Hemingway’s trail,1999 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, West, Ben. (The) Secret life of Ernest Hemingway,1956 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Whitfield, Ellis. Hemingway: el hombre (in Spanish),1953 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Who the hell is Ernest Hemingway?,1956 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Write from your heart,1999 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Auction Catalogs, Christie’s-Ernest Hemingway, including recently discovered manuscript,May 19, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Auction Catalogs, R. M. Smythe-Ernest Hemingway, “Out of the Lyon’s Den”,1996 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Auction Catalogs, Sotheby’s [catalog]- Hemingway, Ernest, letter to Marcelline, and other items,July 1937, December 10, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Book-of-the-Month Club, Correspondence re: For whom the bell tolls,January 6, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Book Reviews of, For whom the bell tolls,1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Book Reviews of, (The) Garden of Eden,1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Books re: Hemingway, El author y su obra Hemingway,1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Brochures, Key West, Florida,1984, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brochures, Oak Park, Illinois,undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Diaries, of George R. Hemingway,1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Diaries, of George R. Hemingway,1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Diaries, of George R. Hemingway,1942, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Diaries, of George R. Hemingway,1945 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Diaries, of George R. Hemingway,1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Diaries, of George R. Hemingway,1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Diaries, of George R. Hemingway,1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Diaries, of George R. Hemingway,1952 (mostly empty) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Donor Correspondence,July 10, 19, 1985; August 3, 1998; October, December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dust Jacket (facsimilie) for (The) Torrents of spring,1928 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Exhibit Brochures, Celebrate the Hemingway centennial at the Kennedy Library; Kennedy Library Newsletter,April 8-11, 1999; 1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Exhibit Brochures, Exhibition of landscapes by Grace Hall Hemingway, Little Traverse History Museum,July 21-September 16, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Exhibit Brochures, Picturing Hemingway: a writer in his time, National Portrait Gallery,June 8-November 7, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Exhibit Photographs, Reception for Hemingway in Michigan, Clarke Historical Library, Central Michigan University,October 17, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Galley Proof, Hemingway in Cuba, by Hilary Hemingway and Charles Brennen,2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Hemingway Society, National Conference at Traverse City, Michigan, Brochures, Materials,September-October 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Ketchum, Spencer, Editorial Projects on Ernest and Sunny Hemingway, related clippings and correspondence; letter from Ernest Mainland and Photograph of Sunny Hemingway Mainland,1987-2003; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Little Traverse Historical Society, Hemingway and Windemere Tour, Tickets and Brochure,1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Manuscripts, Correspondence, Letter from Ernest to “Dear Dad”, October 28, 1919, with certificate of Authenticity signed by Ernest Hemingway Mainland, June 25, 2007. (This letter is housed separately from the rest of the collection.),October 28, 1919; June 25, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Manuscripts, Correspondence, Letter from Ernest to “Dear Mother,” November 11, 1919, envelope November 12, 1919 (This letter is housed separately from the rest of the collection.),November 11-12, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Manuscripts, Correspondence, Letter from Ernest to his friend Jim Gamble, April 18 and 27, 1919. (This letter is housed separately from the rest of the collection.),April 18, 27, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Manuscripts, Correspondence, Letter from Ernest to his son J. H. N. Hemingway, August 2, 1960 (and envelope),August 2, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Articles of Incorporation; By-laws; Goals and Objectives,1993, 1995, 2007; 2000; undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Birth Centennial Celebration, Brochures, Public Relations Materials,July 22-25, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Birth Centennial Celebration, Tote Bag, Cards,July 22-25, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Board Archives (CDs of Email, Minutes, By-laws, Miscellaneous) (moved to Box 7 due to growth rate of folder),2003-2006, 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, etc.,1990-1998 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, etc.,1999 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, etc.,2000-2003 (Scattered) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Financial Statements,1996-2006 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Hemingway Conference, Packet; Brochure,2003; 2005 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Photographs [Conference, Horton Bay and Petoskey, Michigan, tours],1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Photographs and Negatives [Conference],1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Photographs and Negatives [Conference],1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Photographs and Negatives [Conference],1998, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Photographs [Conference, Horton Bay, Michigan],1999 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Movie Press Kit for '(The) Old man and the sea',undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Movie Programs (7, in Swedish),undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Movie Promotion Material, for ‘For whom the bell tolls’, 1943, Copies from Hemingway Family Scrapbooks?,undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Movie Promotion Material, for ‘For whom the bell tolls’, 1943, Copies from the John F. Kennedy Library (3),undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Movie Promotion Material, for ‘For whom the bell tolls’, 1943, Copy from Book World, 1969, of Ernest, Marcelline, Ursula, and Sunny with Owen S. White in 1911, with Madelaine Hemingway Miller’s signature (very acidic),1969 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘Adventures of a young man’,1962 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘Breaking point’,1950 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘(A) Farewell to arms’,[1932] (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘For whom the bell tolls’,[1943] (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘In Love and war’,1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘(The) Killers’,1964 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘(The) Macomber affair’,1946 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘(The) Old man and the sea’,[1958] (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Movie Promotion Material, of Stars, Premier of '(The) Snows of Kilimanjaro',circa 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘To have and have not’,[1944] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Movie Promotion Material, from the movies of, ‘Under my skin’,1950 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Movie Promotion Material, Of Capital of the World (a bull-fight ballet),undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Ernest Hemingway,1927, 1937, circa 1930s, 1953, circa 1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Horton Bay (22), and Digitized Photographs (2 items) and Map (Ohle Photographs),circa 19-20th centuries, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, [Miscellaneous],undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Play, Lovely Walloona, conflict at the Hemingways, by Morris Buske,1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Play Program, (A) Summer with Hemingway’s twin, by Lucia deView,2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Playbills, (The) Fifth column; Papa,1940; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Postcards, Hemingway-Pfieffer Museum and Educational Center; Oak Park, Illinois, home; School, Seney, Michigan,1999; undated; 1912 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Postage Stamps (20-25 cent stamps); 1st day issue, Cancelled; 3 cent stamps (Cuban),undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Screenplay of E. H.’s Adventures of a young man, by A. E. Hotchner, First Draft,May 29, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sheet Music, (A) Farewell to arms, by Allie Wrubel and Abner Silver,1933 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Term Paper, Larson, Marion Kraft. Yes, I knew Ernest Hemingway,1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Theatre Program, includes "(The) Killers",1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Tourism Literature, This week in Paris,November 9-16, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Video, 2003, of ‘Adventures of a young man’ (1962 movie),2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings (copies) [on top due to size],1960s (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings (copies) [on top due to size],1970s (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings (copies) [on top due to size],1980s (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings (copies) [on top due to size],1990s (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings (copies) [on top due to size],2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings (copies) [on top due to size],undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, “Bimini”, Esquire,October 1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, “(The) Cardinal picks a winner”, Ken, v. 1, no. 3,May 5th, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, (The) Dangerous summer, (Part 1 of 3, introduction, and editor’s note, 3 copies), Life,September 5th, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, (The) Dangerous summer, (Part 2 of 3, 2 copies), Life,September 12, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, (The) Dangerous summer, (Part 3 of 3, 2 copies), Life,September 19, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, “Dying badly”, Ken, v. 1, no. 2,September 21, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, (The) Garden of Eden; and article re: Burgess, Anthony. (The) Joys of a new marriage, Life,June 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, (The) Great blue river, Holiday, v. 6, no.1,July 1949 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, H. M.’s loyal state department, Ken, v. 1, no. 6,June 16, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, “Horns of the bull”, Esquire,June 1936 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, “I disavow any responsibility” Part II (concluding the Christmas gift), Life,May 4, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, (The) Killers, Life,September 2, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, “London fights the robots”, Colliers,August 19, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, “Notes of dangerous game: the third Tangayika letter”, Esquire,July 1934 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, (The) Old man and the sea, (2 copies), Life,September 1, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles by Hemingway, Safari, 1954; and Behind the scenes, (2 copies), Look,January 26, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Atkins, John. Hemingway and the --American novel; --Motion picture; --Great outdoors; --Old man and the sea; From the wisdom of Ernest Hemingway, (2 copies),1958 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Campoamor, Fernando. El viejoy y el mar, ((The) Old man and the sea, in Spanish),1957 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Cowley, Malcolm. A Portrait of Mister Papa,1949 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Downes, Robert. (A) Hemingway encounter,April 2004 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Gatti, Armand. Hemingway: le viel homme et aeon coeuer (in French),1959 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Hemingway, Mary. (A) Personal story,1961 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Hemingway, Mary. (A) Sentimental safari; and Hunt, George P., How we got to know the Hemingways,1963 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Hemingway (Photographic essay); MacLesh, Archibald. His mirror was danger; and editor’s note, (3 copies),1961 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Hemingway’s old man and his movie epic,1958 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, His new book: “A Moveable feast”; Hunt, George P. How Hemingway wrote “A Moveable feast”,1964 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Hotchner, A. E. Papa Hemingway, (Part 1 of 3),1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Hotchner, A. E. Papa Hemingway, (Part 2 of 3),1966 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Hotchner, A. E. Papa Hemingway, (Part 3 of 3),1966 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Lockhart, Lloyd. Dropping in on Hemingway; (The) Old man lands biggest catch,1958; 1954 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, (Private Lives column),1937 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Ledger-size magazines with Articles re: (about) Hemingway, (A) Visit with Hemingway,1956 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Sheet Music, Lovely Walloona, words and music by Grace Hall-Hemingway (3 copies),1901 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Photographs (2008 copies) from the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library, Ernest Hemingway, As an Adult (37),2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photographs (2008 copies) from the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library, Ernest Hemingway, And Friends (14),2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Photographs (2008 copies) from the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library, Ernest Hemingway, In Uniform (3),2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photographs (2008 copies) from the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library, Ernest Hemingway, As a Young Boy (8),2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photographs (2008 copies) from the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library, Hadley Hemingway (5),2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Photographs (2008 copies) from the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library, Hemingway Family (14),2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Photographs (2008 copies) from the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library, Hemingway Homes, Cabins, and Related Buildings (24),2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Photographs (2008 copies) from the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library, Hemingway Miscellaneous, Automobiles, Streams, Road, etc. (13),2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Pat Davis, Correspondence and Sheet music, Grace Hall-Hemingway, Clarence Hemingway,1905, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Pat Davis, Newspaper Clippings (copies), Hemingway, Dilworth House, Pat,undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pat Davis, Photographs, 6 (copies), Horton Bay, Michigan,2012 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, (CD), File Names,2012 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, Pre-1994-2005,2012 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, 2005 (folder 1 of 3),2012 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, 2005 (folder 2 of 3),2012 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, 2005 (folder 3 of 3),2012 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, Index of 2012 files, Conference Int’l,2012 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, Index of 2012 files, Conference Int’l, 2012,2012 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, Pre-MHS-IHS,2012 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, Women DVD, MHS, 2012, Incorporation Documents, 1993-1995, 2007, 2009, Mailing Lists, 2010,2012 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society, Archives, Documents and Correspondence, Printouts, Hemingway Review, Spring 2012, Ruebelman, Scrivener, Tour MHS,2012 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Daniello, Vincent. Aboard Pilar with Papa,2014 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, King, Richard. Hemingway’s sharks,2014 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Articles re: (about) Hemingway, Pike, Bill. Tribute to an old man,2011 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society. Board Archives (Financials, Minutes, By-laws, Miscellaneous, Prints, CDs, moved from Box 2 due to growth rate of folder),2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society. Board Archives (Financials, Minutes, By-laws, Miscellaneous, Prints, CDs, moved from Box 2 due to growth rate of folder),2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society. Board Archives (Financials, Minutes, By-laws, Miscellaneous, Prints, CDs, moved from Box 2 due to growth rate of folder),2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society. Board Archives (Financials, Minutes, By-laws, Miscellaneous, Prints, CDs, moved from Box 2 due to growth rate of folder),2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society. Board Archives (Financials, Minutes, By-laws, Miscellaneous, Prints, CDs, moved from Box 2 due to growth rate of folder),2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society. Board Archives (Financials, Minutes, By-laws, Miscellaneous, Prints, CDs, moved from Box 2 due to growth rate of folder), no 2012,2010-2011 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Michigan Hemingway Society. Board Archives (Financials, Minutes, By-laws, Miscellaneous, Prints, CDs, moved from Box 2 due to growth rate of folder),2013- (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Film, ‘Adventures of a young man’, undated, 16 mm film (4 reels in 4 boxes),undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #1, Stamp, Photograph, Stage Adaption of "(A) Farewell to arms," 11x14 inches Elissa Landis, Glenn Anders,1930 (Folder 1)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #1, Stamp, 1st day issue of Key West, Florida, Cancelled Stamp, Matted, (Stamp 8x11 inches, with mat 12x16 inches),undated (Folder 1)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #2, Movie Posters, Lobby Cards, each in color and measuring 11x14 inches, ‘Adventures of a young man’, posters #1-8,1962 (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #2, Movie Posters, Lobby Cards, each in color and measuring 11x14 inches, ‘A Bout Portant (‘(The) Killers’ in French), posters #1-4, 6-7,1964 (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #2, Movie Posters, Lobby Cards, each in color and measuring 11x14 inches, ‘(A) Farewell to arms’, posters #1-8,1957 (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #2, Movie Posters, Lobby Cards, each in color and measuring 11x14 inches, ‘For whom the bell tolls’, poster #7,1957 (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #2, Movie Posters, Lobby Cards, each in color and measuring 11x14 inches, ‘(The) Gun runners’, posters #2-8,1959 (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #2, Movie Posters, Lobby Cards, each in color and measuring 11x14 inches, ‘(The) Snows of Kilimanjaro’, posters #2-5, 7-8,1952 (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #2, Movie Posters, Lobby Cards, each in color and measuring 11x14 inches ‘(The) Sun also rises’, poster #1,1957 (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #2, Movie Advertisement, "(The) Macomber affair',1946 (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #3, Posters not Advertising Movies, Ernest Hemingway y Cuba Posters, by Instituto Cubano del Libro, black and white, 11.5x16.5 inches, Two men on a bridge,undated (Folder 3)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #3, Posters not Advertising Movies, Ernest Hemingway y Cuba Posters, by Instituto Cubano del Libro, black and white, 11.5x16.5 inches, Man on a bridge (Hemingway?),undated (Folder 3)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #3A, 'El Valor de ser hombre posters (2, in Spanish), both measuring 12.5x16.5 inches,undated (Folder 3)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #3A, '(The) Killers', Universal City Studios Showman Manual,1964 (Folder 3)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Larger Posters, Movie Posters, in color, ‘Trafiquants d’armes a Cuba ((The) Gun runners)’, (printed in Belgium), Window Card, 14x20 inches,[1958] (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Larger Posters, Movie Posters, in color, ‘‘Adventures de Jeunesse’, (in French), Window Card, 17.5x22 inches,undated (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Larger Posters, Movie Posters, in color, ‘L’adieu aux armes ((A) Farewell to arms)’, (in French, printed in Belgium), Window Card, 15x22 inches,[1957] (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Larger Posters, Movie Posters, in color, ‘Adventures of a young man’, Half Sheet, 22x28 inches,1962 (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Larger Posters, Movie Posters, in color, ‘(The) Snows of Kilimanjaro’, Half Sheet, 22x28 inches,1952 (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Posters Not Advertising Movies, Michigan in Hemingway: a sense of place, Michigan Hemingway Society, birth centennial celebration, Petoskey, Michigan, in shades of brown, 14x17 inches (2 copies, 1 signed)July 22-25, 1999 (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Posters Not Advertising Movies, Hemingway (portrait?), by F. Paehr (sp?), in color, 16x20 inches,circa 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Posters Not Advertising Movies, Hemingway up in Michigan II, Stafford Perry Hotel, Petoskey, Michigan, in shades of brown, 16.5x23 inches,October 17-20, 1991 (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folders: Folder #4, Posters Not Advertising Movies, To have and have not, a celebration of Hemingway’s years in Key West and Havana, black and white photograph of Hemingway and sword fish, on black background with white lettering, 17x22 inches,April 29, 1995 (Folder 4)